Register of the Atlantic Council of the United States Records, 1950-1986
Hoover Institution Archives
- SUBJECT FILE, 1950-1985
  - Conferences
    - Japan: It's Rising Challenge to U.S. Business, Washington, D.C., November 7-8, 1973 (Folder 11)
    - "NATO: Problems and Prospects," Center for Strategic Studies, Georgetown University, May 7-8, 1964 (Folder 12)
    - Ninth National Conference of the U.S. Commission for UNESCO, Chicago, October 23-26, 1963 (125, Folder 1)
    - Non-tariff Barriers (NTB) Conference, 1970 (Folder 2)
    - Second Annual Atlantic Community Conference, April 14-15, 1967 (Folder 3)
    - Texas and Indiana, 1965 (Folder 4)
    - UN Conference on the Human Environment, Stockholm, June 1972 (Folder 5)
    - University of Wisconsin (U.S. foreign policy), March 1965 (Folder 6)
    - Washington World Conference on World Peace Through Law, September 12-18, 1965 (Folder 7)
    - Young Leaders Conference, Portugal, November 20-22, 1969 (Folder 8)
  - Conferences for Corporation Executives
    - 1971-72 (Folder 9)
    - 1974 (Folder 10)
  - CONTAC
    - 1965-66 (Folder 11)
    - 1981 (Folder 12)
    - Georgetown University, November 1967 (Folder 13)
  - Contemporary Affairs Society (Folder 14)
  - Contributions
    - 1962-63 (Folder 15)
    - 1968-69 (Folder 16)
    - 1977-78 (Folder 17)
  - Contributors
    - General (Folder 18)
    - Corporations, 1968 (Folder 19)
  - Coordination Committee proposal, 1968 (Folder 20)
  - Copyrights (126, Folder 1)
  - Corbet, Hugh (Folder 2)
  - Corbett, David E., "Atlantica: The New Dimension,", 1966 (Folder 3)
  - Corporate Committee
    - 1974 (Folder 4)
    - 1974-76 (Folder 5)
  - Corporate contibutors, 1965 (Folder 6)
  - Corporate members, 1974 (Folder 7-8)
  - Corporations in the U.S. ranked by assets, 1957 (Folder 9)
  - Corterier, Peter (Folder 10)
  - COSERV (Folder 11)
  - Council for Advancement of Secondary Education
    - General (Folder 12)
    - Meeting, June 1, 1967 (Folder 13)
  - Council for European Studies (Folder 14)
  - Council of Europe, 1962-63 (127, Folder 1)
  - Council of Foreign Relations (Aubrey, Henry) (Folder 2)
  - Council on Foreign Relations
    - 1975-76 (Folder 3)
    - Meeting, November 29, 1962 (Folder 4)
  - Council on International Economic Policy (CIEP), 1974 (Folder 5)
  - Crathorne, Lord, visit of, May 1963 (Folder 6)
  - Critical Issues Council (Folder 7)
  - Crotonville Conference, 1965
    - General (Folder 8)
    - Clippings (Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1965-66 (Folder 10)
    - Draft report (Folder 11)
    - Final reports (Folder 12)
    - Final reports (128, Folder 1)
    - Follow-up on (Folder 2)
    - Planning (Folder 3)
    - Report (Folder 4)
    - Requests for report (Folder 5)
  - CSCE/MBFR, 1972-73 (Folder 6)
  - Current projects, 1973 (Folder 7)
  - Curriculum vitae and resumes (Folder 8-10)
  - Curriculum vitae and resumes (129, Folder 1)
  - Dacor House
    - General (Folder 2)
    - Reception, October 26, 1970 (Folder 3)
  - Danielian, N. R., statement before the House Ways and Means Committee, April 3, 1973 (Folder 4)
  - Data, Inc., 1968 (Folder 5)
  - Debre, Michel, luncheon, January 30, 1981 (Folder 6)
  - Debt financing (Folder 7-10)
  - Debt financing (130, Folder 1-2)
  - De Carmoy, Guy (Folder 3)
  - Declaration of Atlantic Unity
    - 1964 (Folder 4)
    - 1965 (Folder 5)
    - 1966 (Folder 6-7)
    - 1967 (131, Folder 1)
  - Declaration of Paris, January 19, 1962 (Folder 2)
  - De Gaulle, General (Folder 3)
  - Democratic Platform Committee
    - 1972 (Folder 4)
    - General (Folder 5)
    - Chairmen (Folder 6)
    - Wallace, Richard J., statement before, August 19, 1968 (Folder 7)
  - Detente Diplomacy: U.S. and European Security in the 1970s
    - Book reviews (Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (Folder 9)
    - Press lists (Folder 10)
    - Promotion, publication, distribution (Folder 11)
  - Deutsche Atlantische Gesellschaft (Folder 12)
  - Development Alternatives, Inc. (Folder 13)
  - Development Working Group
    - 1976 (Folder 14-15)
    - General (132, Folder 1-7)
    - General (133, Folder 1)
    - Martin, Edwin M., draft of speech, April 1976 (Folder 2)
    - Pearson, Charles, "Environment and Ocean Issues in North-South Relations,", April 1976 (Folder 3)
    - Ramis, Gustav, paper (Folder 4)
    - Rubin, Seymour, paper, December 1975 (Folder 5)
  - Direct Investment and the Multi-National Corporation (Folder 6-7)
  - Directory of sponsors
    - 1964 (Folder 8)
    - 1969 (Folder 9)
  - Ditchley Foundation
    - General (Folder 10)
    - Conference, June 2-5, 1967 (Folder 11)
  - Dobbs, James (Folder 12)
  - Documents sent out, 1964-65 (Folder 13)
  - Domestic International Sales Corporation (DISC) (Folder 14)
  - Draft resolution, 1965 (Folder 15)
  - Drafting Committee, 1967 (134, Folder 1)
  - Drummond, Roscoe and Gene Bradley, article, April 8, 1968 (Folder 2)
  - Dunellen Publishing Company (Folder 3)
  - East-West trade
    - General (Folder 4-6)
    - Articles and drafts (Folder 7)
    - Banking and finance (Folder 8)
    - Bibliographies (135, Folder 1)
    - Bureau of East-West Trade (Folder 2)
    - China (Folder 3)
    - Contract and correspondence (Folder 4)
    - Correspondence
      - 1974
        - April-August (Folder 5)
        - September-October (Folder 6)
        - November-December (Folder 7)
      - 1975
        - January-February (Folder 8)
        - March-April (Folder 9)
        - May-June (Folder 10)
        - July-October (Folder 11)
        - November-December (136, Folder 1)
      - 1976
        - January-May (Folder 2)
        - June-October (Folder 3)
    - Correspondence and memoranda, 1974 (Folder 4)
    - Council for Mutual Economic Assistance (CMEA) (Folder 5)
    - Documents (Folder 6)
    - Economics
      - General (Folder 7)
      - Czech-G.D.R. (Folder 8)
      - Hungary-U.S.S.R. (Folder 9)
    - Evans, John W. (Folder 10)
    - Evans and Reinstein travel report, November 1974 (Folder 11)
    - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (G.A.T.T.)
      - General (Folder 12)
      - Poland (Folder 13)
    - JWH's comments on East-West draft paper (Folder 14)
    - KT (137, Folder 1)
    - Martin, Edwin M., "The U.S. and the Developing Countries,", November 1976 (Folder 2)
    - Multinationals, Western (Folder 3)
    - Notes (Folder 4)
    - Nuclear weapons (Folder 5)
    - Policy study outline (Folder 6)
    - Proposal, April 8, 1974 (Folder 7)
    - Protto Report (Folder 8)
    - Publications and information to be obtained (Folder 9)
    - Reinstein, Jacques (Folder 10)
    - Report of interviews in Europe, November 1974 (Folder 11)
    - Reports for memoranda of, September 30, 1975 (Folder 12)
    - Sattler, James F. (138, Folder 1)
    - Steering Committee
      - General (Folder 2)
      - Meetings
        - 1974 (Folder 3)
        - 1975 (Folder 4-5)
        - 1976 (Folder 6-7)
    - Study (Folder 8)
    - Technology transfer (Folder 9)
    - Trade
      - General (Folder 10)
      - Communist countries (139, Folder 1)
      - Conference on Security and Cooperation in Europe, Helsinki consultations (Folder 2)
      - NATO trade with communist countries (Folder 3)
      - Peoples Republic of China (Folder 4)
      - U.S.S.R. (Folder 5)
    - Trade Act of, 1974 (Folder 6)
    - Trade restrictions, U.S. liberalization of (Folder 7)
    - U.S. legislation (Folder 8)
    - U.S.-U.S.S.R. Trade and Economic Council (Folder 9)
    - Work Program (Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous (Folder 11-12)
    - Miscellaneous (cont.) (140, Folder 1-3)
  - Eastman Kodak Company
    - 1970-72 (Folder 4)
    - 1973 (Folder 5-6)
    - 1975 (Folder 7)
    - 1975 (141, Folder 1)
    - 1976 (Folder 2)
  - Eberle, W. D., remarks, Tokyo, May 19, 1972 (Folder 3)
  - Ecology-environment, 1970 (Folder 4)
  - "Economic Growth for the 1970s," Geneva, Switzerland, May/June 1966 (Folder 6)
  - Economic Policy Working Group (Folder 7)
  - "Economic Problems,", November 1966 (Folder 8)
  - Economic summit, 1978 (Folder 9)
  - Economics
    - General (Folder 10)
    - Textbook drafts (Folder 11)
  - Education
    - General (Folder 12)
    - Meeting, August 25, 1974 (142, Folder 1)
  - Eighth Atlantic Study Conference, Oxford, September 6-11, 1970 (Folder 2)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D., possible article for Reader's Digest, n.d. (Folder 3)
  - Eisenhower article, 1968 (Folder 4)
  - Eisenhower Library (Folder 5)
  - Emanuelli, Pierre
    - General (Folder 6)
    - Tour, August-September 1962 (Folder 7)
    - Visit of, June 1969 (Folder 8)
  - Emergency Committee for American Trade (ECAT) (Folder 9)
  - Emminger, Otmar, "Inflation and the International Monetary System,", 1973 (Folder 10)
  - Employees earnings, 1963 (Folder 11)
  - Employment applications
    - 1968 (Folder 12)
    - 1969 (Folder 13)
    - 1969-1970 (143, Folder 1)
    - 1970 (Folder 2)
    - 1971-72 (Folder 3)
    - 1973 (Folder 4)
    - 1974 (Folder 5)
    - 1975 (Folder 6-7)
  - Energy
    - General (144, Folder 1-6)
    - General (cont.) (145, Folder 1-2)
    - Canada (Folder 3)
    - CIA/GAO bibliographies (Folder 4)
    - Congressional Committees bibliographies (Folder 5)
    - International (Folder 6)
    - Library of Congress (Folder 7)
    - Soviet Union (146, Folder 1-3)
    - United States (Folder 4-5)
  - Energy Committee
    - 1973 (Folder 6)
    - 1974 (Folder 7-8)
    - 1975 (147, Folder 1)
    - Achilles, Theodore C. (Folder 2-3)
    - Burgess, W. Randolph (Folder 4)
    - Cleveland, Harlan (Folder 5)
    - Gray, John (Folder 6)
    - Levy, Walter (Folder 7)
    - Meeting, January 25, 1974 (Folder 8)
    - Memoranda (Folder 9)
    - Press releases (148, Folder 1)
    - Proposed rapporteurs (Folder 2)
    - Sonnenfeldt, Helmut (Folder 3)
    - Woodard, Kim (Folder 4)
    - Working Groups (Folder 5-6)
  - Energy Committee, Group III, draft reports, 1974 (Folder 7)
  - Energy crisis and world food production, 1974 (Folder 8)
  - Energy Policy Committee
    - 1980-81 (Folder 9)
    - 1981 (Folder 10-11)
  - Energy Project
    - General, 1975 (149, Folder 1-2)
    - Correspondence
      - 1973
        - January-August (Folder 3)
        - October-December (Folder 4)
      - 1973-75 (Folder 5)
      - 1974
        - January (Folder 6)
        - February-May (Folder 7)
        - June-December (Folder 8)
      - Love, John A., 1973 (Folder 9)
    - Documents, information (150, Folder 1-2)
    - Drafts and notes (Folder 3-4)
    - Funds (Folder 5)
    - Nuclear fuels (Folder 6)
    - Nuclear fuels (151, Folder 1)
    - OECD energy assessment and data base (Folder 2)
    - Policy papers, 1975 (Folder 3)
    - Rapporteurs meeting, September 4, 1974 (Folder 4)
    - Steering Committee
      - Meetings (Folder 5)
      - Paper (Folder 6)
    - Van Lennep interview, Le Monde, December 10, 1974 (Folder 7)
    - Working Group I (Folder 8-9)
    - Working Group I (152, Folder 1)
    - Working Group II
      - Meetings, 1974 (Folder 2)
      - Paper, 1974-75 (Folder 3)
    - Working Group III
      - Meetings, 1974-75 (Folder 4)
      - Paper, 1974 (Folder 5)
    - Working papers (Folder 6)
  - Energy Steering Committee, 1974 (Folder 7)
  - Engelhard, Charles W., "Free Trade for a Free World,", December 9, 1961 (Folder 8)
  - Environment
    - General (153, Folder 1)
    - Canada survey, 1975 (Folder 2)
    - U.S. House of Representatives testimony (Folder 3)
  - Environmental Conference, 1971 (Folder 4)
  - Environmental Debate, 1970 (Folder 5)
  - "Environmental Economics," outline, n.d. (Folder 6)
  - Equipment rental
    - 1961-63 (Folder 7)
    - 1964 (Folder 8)
  - Erickson, John, "Trends in the Soviet Combined Arms Concept,", 1977 (Folder 9)
  - Ermath, Fritz (Folder 10)
  - Europe-America Conference, Amsterdam, March 1973 (Folder 11-12)
  - Europe and America - The Next Ten Years
    - General (Folder 13)
    - Book reviews (Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1971 (Folder 15)
  - "European-American Business Climate,", August 8, 1967 (154, Folder 1)
  - European-American relations, 1971 (Folder 2)
  - European Atlantic publications, 1961-62 (Folder 3)
  - European communities, 1973-74 (Folder 4)
  - European Community Information Service, 1960 (Folder 5)
  - European North American Committee (EURNAC) (Folder 6)
  - European research groups, 1975 (Folder 7)
  - European security, 1971 (Folder 8)
  - European Security Conference, January 1970 (Folder 9)
  - European trip to the U.S., April 1964 (Folder 10)
  - European Young Leaders (Folder 11)
  - Executive Committee meetings
    - December 8, 1961 (Folder 12)
    - February 2, 1962 (Folder 13)
  - Expenses
    - 1962-63 (Folder 14)
    - 1969 (Folder 15)
  - Export trading companies (155, Folder 1-2)
  - Exxon luncheon, March 13, 1974 (Folder 3)
  - Faure, Maurice (Folder 4)
  - Federal Energy Administration, 1974 (Folder 5)
  - Federal Union
    - 1965-67 (Folder 6)
    - 1970 (Folder 7)
    - 1971 (Folder 8)
    - 1972-73 (Folder 9)
    - 1974 (Folder 10)
    - 1975 (Folder 11)
    - 1976-77 (Folder 12)
  - Federal withholding tax, 1962 (Folder 13)
  - Federalism (Folder 14)
  - Fenton, Richard C., statement before the International Chamber of Commerce Congress, May 17, 1967 (Folder 15)
  - FICA and income tax withheld, 1968 (Folder 16)
  - Fifth Biennial Atlantic Study Conference on Education, Washington, D.C.., September 7-12, 1964 (156, Folder 1-2)
  - Finance Committee
    - 1968 (Folder 3)
    - 1974 (Folder 4)
  - Finances
    - 1962-63 (Folder 5)
    - 1967-69 (Folder 6)
    - 1973 (Folder 7)
    - 1973-74 (Folder 8)
    - 1978 (Folder 9)
  - Financial statements, 1962 (Folder 10)
  - Finer, Herman, "The Common Market,", 1961 (Folder 11)
  - Finley, Martha C., correspondence
    - 1973 (Folder 12)
    - 1975 (Folder 13)
    - 1976 January-July (Folder 14)
    - 1978 (Folder 15)
    - 1979 (Folder 16)
  - Fleming College (157, Folder 1)
  - "The Floating Rate System: The Search for Balance and Stability,", November 1978 (Folder 2)
  - Fontainebleau Conference report (Folder 3)
  - Fontenay, Charles (Folder 4)
  - Food and hunger, 1978 (Folder 5)
  - Ford Foundation
    - 1963-68 (Folder 6)
    - 1967 (Folder 7)
    - "Securing the Sea,", 1976 (Folder 8)
  - Ford Foundation Project, 1974-77 (Folder 9)
  - Foreign Affairs Forum, April/May 1967 (Folder 10)
  - Foreign Affairs Research Institute, 1978-79 (Folder 11)
  - Foreign foundations (Folder 12)
  - Foreign language editors (Folder 13)
  - Foreign Policy Association
    - 1962-68 (Folder 14)
    - General (158, Folder 1-5)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary Dinner, January 25, 1968
      - General (Folder 6)
      - General (159, Folder 1-3)
      - Committee correspondence and lists (Folder 4)
      - Correspondence (Folder 5)
      - Press invitations (Folder 6)
    - "Fifty Years - The Story of the Foreign Policy Association, ", 1918-1968 (Folder 7)
  - Foreign Policy Research Institute (University of Pennsylvania) (Folder 8)
  - Foreign Student Service Council (Folder 9)
  - Forgash, Morris, "A Plan for an International Bank for Economic Acceleration of Backward Countries,", 1961 (Folder 10)
  - Forgash, Morris, "A Plan for an International Bank for Economic Acceleration of Backward Countries,", 1961 (160, Folder 1)
  - Form letters (Folder 2)
  - Foulon Group, 1980 (Folder 3-4)
  - Foundation approach
    - 1972 (Folder 5)
    - Labor study (Folder 6)
    - Monetary proposal (Folder 7)
  - Foundation requests (Folder 8)
  - Fowler, Henry H.
    - General (Folder 9-10)
    - Correspondence
      - 1973 (Folder 11)
      - 1974 January-June (Folder 12)
      - 1974-76 (Folder 13)
      - 1975 (161, Folder 1)
      - 1975-76 (Folder 2)
      - 1976-77 (Folder 3)
      - 1977 (Folder 4)
      - 1978 (Folder 5)
    - Dinner at Yale Club, November 26, 1973 (Folder 6)
    - Platform policy statement (Folder 7)
    - Speech re: anti-trust laws, October 17, 1964 (Folder 8)
    - Speech, Zurich, October 26, 1977 (Folder 9)
    - Statement before the International Economics Sub- committee of the Joint Economic Committee, U.S. Congress, October 10, 1975 (Folder 10)
    - Troop reduction testimony, 1973 (Folder 11)
  - Frank, Paul, "Security Problems in the Light of the Moscow Treaty" (Folder 12)
  - Free Trade Area (Folder 13)
  - French Association for the Atlantic Community, visit of, September 1964 (Folder 14)
  - French chemists' visit, May 1967 (Folder 15)
  - French industrialists and bankers, April 1969 (Folder 16)
  - French politics, 1968 (Folder 17)
  - French university students' visit, July-August 1970 (Folder 18)
  - French visit
    - 1962 August-September
      - General (Folder 19)
      - Reception (162, Folder 1)
    - 1963 October (Folder 2)
  - French visitors, November 1968 (Folder 3)
  - Fulbright, J. W., "For a Concept of Free Nations," reprint, Foreign Affairs, October 1961 (Folder 4)
  - Fundraising
    - 1964-66 (Folder 5)
    - 1968 (Folder 6)
    - 1969 (Folder 7)
    - 1970 (Folder 8)
    - 1970-71 (Folder 9)
    - 1973-75 (Folder 10)
    - 1974 (Folder 11)
    - 1977-78 (Folder 12)
    - Oram Associates, Inc., 1966-67 (Folder 13)
    - Reports
      - 1968 (Folder 14)
      - 1969 (Folder 15)
  - Furniture and equipment, 1964 (Folder 16)
  - Gallup Opinion Index, 1970 (Folder 17)
  - Garmise, Bert, Associates
    - Correspondence, 1968-1972 (Folder 18)
    - Promotion, Fall 1971 (Folder 19)
  - Garver, John W. (163, Folder 1)
  - Gasteyger, Curt (Folder 2)
  - GATT, meeting, Paris, June 1977 (Folder 3)
  - GATT Plus, 1975 (Folder 4)
  - Geiger, Theodore and Sperry Lea, "The Free Trade Area Concept As Applied to the United States,", October 1967 (Folder 5)
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade, meeting, February 27-28, 1969 (Folder 6)
  - General Electric Company
    - 1962-63 (Folder 7)
    - 1967 (Folder 8)
  - Georgetown interns, 1976-78 (Folder 9)
  - Georgetown University
    - Banker's Forum, October 1965 (Folder 10)
    - Center for Strategic and International Studies (Folder 11)
    - Proposal to improve the study of international inter- dependence, 1977 (Folder 12)
  - German Atlantic Association, visit of members, May 1970 (Folder 13)
  - German Atlantic Society, 1963-1971 (Folder 14-15)
  - German Marshall Fund, 1974-79 (Folder 16)
  - German visit, September 1964 (Folder 17)
  - Ginn's, 1968-69 (164, Folder 1)
  - Glennan, T. Keith, "Technology and Foreign Affairs,", October 1976 (Folder 2)
  - Goedhart, Frans J., Report of the Political Committee on the Atlantic Convention of NATO Nations, n.d. (Folder 3)
  - Goldwater, Barry (Folder 4)
  - Goodman, H. I., "The Changing World Energy Picture and Prospects of the Future,", May 30, 1980 (Folder 5)
  - Goodpaster, Andrew J., "The Growing Dimensions of Security,", 1978 (Folder 6)
  - Government funding, policy on (Folder 7)
  - Grants
    - 1976-77 (Folder 8)
    - 1979 (Folder 9)
  - Gray Area
    - General (Folder 10-11)
    - Meeting, April 9, 1979 (Folder 12)
    - Press (Folder 13)
    - Sub-group (Folder 14)
  - Greek-Turkish letter, 1978 (Folder 15)
  - Greek-Turkish study, 1978 (165, Folder 1)
  - Griffiths, William K., "United States Export Policy and the Export Trading Company Act of " 1980 (Folder 2)
  - Group Hospitalization Insurance, 1968 (Folder 3)
  - Gruenther, General, speaking engagement, April 16, 1968 (Folder 4)
  - Guillaume, Gilbert, address to the Council of the North Atlantic Treaty Association, February 5, 1965 (Folder 5)
  - Gutmanis, Ivars (Folder 6)
  - Hadik, Laszlo (Folder 7)
  - Hamburg meeting, November 1974 (Folder 8)
  - Harmel Exercise (Folder 9)
  - Harmel Report, 1968 (Folder 10)
  - "Harmonizing Economic Policy,", May 1977
    - General (Folder 11-13)
    - General (166, Folder 1-2)
    - Achilles, Theodore C., memoranda
      - 1975 March 18 (Folder 3)
      - 1977 March 25 (Folder 4)
    - Drafts (Folder 5-7)
    - Drafts (167, Folder 1-2)
    - Foreword (Folder 3)
    - Guertin draft, 2/1/77 (Folder 4)
    - Leddy comments, March 1977 (Folder 5)
    - Press release, May 1, 1977 (Folder 6)
    - Rowney comments, 2/18/77 (Folder 7)
    - Summit meetings and collective leadership (Folder 8-9)
  - Harned, Joseph W.
    - Board meeting notes, January 20, 1971 (Folder 10)
    - Correspondence
      - 1963-64 (Folder 11)
      - 1964 (168, Folder 1)
      - 1964-65 (Folder 2)
      - 1965-66 (Folder 3)
      - 1966-67 (Folder 4)
      - 1967-68 (Folder 5)
    - London meeting, June 1974 (Folder 6)
    - Program reports, 1970 (Folder 7)
    - Rottach-Egern Conference, June 1974 (Folder 8)
    - Trips
      - 1971
        - March (Emanuelli) (169, Folder 1)
        - (Europe), May-June (Folder 2-3)
        - Spring (Jean P. Boisivon) (Folder 4)
      - 1972
        - April (Bonn) (Folder 5)
        - May (Louisville) (Folder 6)
        - (Europe), May-June (Folder 7)
        - June
          - German-American Conference (Folder 8)
          - London (Folder 9)
      - 1973
        - April (Hudson Institute) (Folder 10)
        - June (Folder 11)
        - June (170, Folder 1-2)
        - Fall
          - Columbus (Folder 3)
          - Tokyo (Folder 4)
          - Travel arrangements (Folder 5-6)
        - October-November
          - General (Folder 7)
          - Honolulu (Folder 8)
          - London (Folder 9)
        - (Pittsburgh), October 1-2 (171, Folder 1)
      - (Paris), 1974 May (Folder 2)
    - US-Japan Trade Council luncheon, May 24, 1977 (Folder 3)
  - Harr, Karl G., statement before the Committee on Ways and Means, U.S. House of Representatives, May 14, 1973 (171, Folder 4)
  - Hartley, Livingston
    - 1967 (Folder 5)
    - In memoriam (Folder 6)
    - Outline of International Agreement Establishing an Atlantic Assembly, April 19, 1962 (Folder 7)
    - Payroll information (Folder 8)
  - Hatfield, Wilma (Folder 9)
  - "Hegemony" (Folder 10)
  - Herter, Christian
    - General (Folder 11-12)
    - "Toward an Atlantic Community,", January 1962 (Folder 13)
  - Herter-Clayton Report, November 2, 1961 (Folder 14)
  - Hickerson, John D., correspondence, 1971 (Folder 15)
  - Hillenbrand, Martin J. (172, Folder 1-2)
  - Huntley, James R.
    - 1971 (Folder 4-5)
    - 1972 (Folder 6)
    - 1973 (Folder 7)
    - 1974 (Folder 8)
    - 1975 (Folder 9)
    - 1976 (173, Folder 1)
    - 1978 (Folder 2)
    - General (Folder 3)
    - "Britain Enters the Common Market: What Does It Mean to America,", February 2, 1972 (Folder 4)
    - Correspondence
      - 1969-1970 (Folder 5)
      - 1971 (Folder 6)
      - 1974 (Folder 7)
      - 1980-81 (Folder 8)
    - "The Future of Federal Union,", January 1981 (Folder 9)
    - Speeches, 1963-64 (Folder 10)
  - IBM (174, Folder 1)
  - Implementation Committee, 1964-65 (Folder 2)
  - Income tax withheld, 1963 (Folder 3)
  - Inflation (Folder 4)
  - Institute of International Education (Folder 5)
  - Institute of World Affairs, USC, 1966 (Folder 6)
  - Institute on World Affairs (San Diego State College) (Folder 7)
  - Institutes of Altantic Studies (Folder 8)
  - Insurance
    - 1962 (Folder 9)
    - 1963 (Folder 10)
    - 1964 (Folder 11)
    - 1968 (Folder 12)
    - 1969 (Folder 13)
  - Inter-American Bank (Folder 14)
  - Inter-University Conference, Berkeley and Stanford, 1965 (Folder 15)
  - Inter-University Faculty Seminar, University of Denver, 1966 (Folder 16)
  - International Business Management Development Program (Folder 17)
  - International Communications Project (Folder 18)
  - International Conference on Canada and the Atlantic Economic Community, November 14-18, 1966 (Folder 19)
  - International Cooperation Year, 1965 (Folder 20)
  - International Management and Development Institute
    - 1972-73 (Folder 21)
    - 1973 (175, Folder 1)
    - 1974-76 (Folder 2)
    - 1975 (Folder 3-4)
    - 1976 (Folder 5-6)
    - 1976 (176, Folder 1)
    - 1977 (Folder 2-3)
    - 1977-78 (Folder 4-5)
    - 1979-1981 (Folder 6)
  - International Monetary Fund (Folder 7)
  - International Monetary System (Folder 8)
  - International Monetary System (177, Folder 1)